[
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum reported success rate for endourological management of UPJO according to the article?",
        "answer": "80%"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was laparoscopic pyeloplasty first introduced?",
        "answer": "1993"
    },
    {
        "question": "What criteria were used to define radiologic success after laparoscopic pyeloplasty?",
        "answer": "Imaging of a patent UPJ on IVP and resolution of obstruction on a MAG-3 renal scan."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the overall success rate of laparoscopic pyeloplasty according to the findings presented in the article?",
        "answer": "87.7%"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was identified as the only risk factor related to the overall failure of laparoscopic pyeloplasty?",
        "answer": "Drained amount"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capsaicin 8% patch used to treat?",
        "answer": "The capsaicin 8% patch is used to treat peripheral neuropathic pain in nondiabetic adults."
    },
    {
        "question": "How does capsaicin in the patch provide pain relief?",
        "answer": "Capsaicin provides pain relief by reversible defunctionalization of nociceptive nerve fibers, resulting in reduced spontaneous nerve activity and loss of responsiveness to sensory stimuli."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the common adverse effects associated with the capsaicin 8% patch?",
        "answer": "The common adverse effects include transient localized reactions such as application-site burning, pain, erythema, and pruritus."
    },
    {
        "question": "How often can treatments with the capsaicin 8% patch be repeated?",
        "answer": "Treatments with the capsaicin 8% patch may be repeated every 90 days if necessary."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why do the authors believe that physician supervision for administering the capsaicin 8% patch is unnecessary?",
        "answer": "The authors believe physician supervision is unnecessary because the application procedure is clearly defined, straightforward, well tolerated, and has been successfully carried out by nurses without physician presence, demonstrating that trained healthcare professionals can administer the patch safely."
    },
    {
        "question": "What organism is considered the third-most frequent nosocomial pathogen among non-fermentative bacteria?",
        "answer": "Stenotrophomonas maltophilia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What commonality is shared between patients with Stenotrophomonas maltophilia bacteremia (SMB) in both the previously reported cases and in the findings from the Japanese hospitals?",
        "answer": "A high ICU admission rate, longer hospital stay before SMB onset, and a high comorbidity of malignancy."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the primary sites of infection for SMB in the Japanese study?",
        "answer": "Central line-associated bloodstream infections were the most common, followed by respiratory and abdominal infections."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the relationship between the prognosis of patients with SMB and the administered antimicrobials in the Japanese study?",
        "answer": "The prognosis of the patients was associated with the underlying diseases and clinical severity but not with the administered antimicrobials."
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of the patients in the Japanese study were administered carbapenem upon their diagnosis with SMB?",
        "answer": "More than one-third of the patients."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some of the advantages of glass ionomer cement (GIC)?",
        "answer": "The advantages of glass ionomer cement include physical/chemical bonding to tooth structure, anticariogenic property due to fluoride release, esthetics, and low coefficient of thermal expansion."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is GIC typically used only in low stress-bearing areas?",
        "answer": "GIC is typically used only in low stress-bearing areas because of its poor mechanical properties, such as low fracture strength, toughness, and wear resistance."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of conditioning a cavity before GIC restoration?",
        "answer": "Conditioning a cavity before GIC restoration removes the smear layer, partially demineralizes and penetrates the superficial dentin surface to enhance the bonding of the GIC to the tooth."
    },
    {
        "question": "How are voids in GIC restorations evaluated in the study?",
        "answer": "Voids in GIC restorations are evaluated using a stereomicroscope after sectioning the samples, and the number of distinct, round voids within the cement are counted."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the study, how does the mechanical mixing of encapsulated GIC compare to hand-mixed GIC in terms of voids?",
        "answer": "The study found that encapsulated GIC had more voids within the cement compared to hand-mixed GIC."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the age and sex of the cat that underwent a glenoidectomy?",
        "answer": "A 15-year-old neutered female cat."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of injury did the cat sustain that led to the glenoidectomy procedure?",
        "answer": "The cat had a comminuted fracture of the right glenoid and scapular neck secondary to a gunshot injury."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is glenoidectomy presented as an alternative to in this case report?",
        "answer": "Glenoidectomy is presented as an alternative to amputation in cats with normal neurovascular supply to the affected limb."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the indications for the use of complete or partial excision of the scapula as mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "The reported indications for complete or partial excision of the scapula are fracture of the glenoid, chronic medial glenohumeral luxation, or more frequently, scapular neoplasia."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the clinical outcomes for the cat post-glenoidectomy?",
        "answer": "The cat experienced persistent functional, pain-free lameness, muscle hypertrophy and changes in shoulder range of motion."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are tonsilloliths and how do they form?",
        "answer": "Tonsilloliths are white or yellowish calcified structures of bacteria and organic debris that commonly develop in enlarged tonsillar crypts. They form when bacteria colonize an epithelial or mucosal surface within a biofilm and eventually calcify, progressing from a soft gel to hard concretions."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main components of tonsilloliths?",
        "answer": "Tonsilloliths are composed of calcium hydroxyapatite and calcium carbonate, along with other minerals including phosphorus, ammonia and magnesium."
    },
    {
        "question": "What symptoms did the 17-year-old female patient present with?",
        "answer": "The 17-year-old female patient presented with a two-year history of recurrent tonsillitis, persistent left-sided oral cavity swelling, dysphagia, foreign body sensation, 'hot potato' speech, and progressively worsening dysphagia."
    },
    {
        "question": "How are bacteria in biofilms and their relation to tonsilloliths significant?",
        "answer": "Bacteria in biofilms are difficult to treat with antibiotics because they are localised and can act as a nidus for acute infection, which leads to a high recurrence rate and chronicity of otorhinolaryngology infections. Similarly, tonsilloliths are a localized concentration of bacteria that can cause recurrent inflammation such as tonsillitis."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the possible presentations of large tonsilloliths and the general approach for their management?",
        "answer": "Large tonsilloliths can present symptomatically with dysphagia, recurrent sore throat, foreign body sensation, or referred otalgia, and halitosis. They may require surgical excision and tonsillectomy if associated with recurrent tonsillitis or if there is a suspicion of malignancy."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the reported prevalence rates of polycystic ovarian syndrome among women of fertility age in Isfahan, Iran, according to Ghanbari's 2010 study?",
        "answer": "7% based on NIH scale, 15.2% based on Rotterdam scale, and 7.92% based on AES."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the common signs of polycystic ovarian syndrome?",
        "answer": "Polycystic ovaries on sonography, disorders in ovulation, irregular menstruation cycles, clinical hyperandrogenism, hirsutism, adulthood acne or acute acne in adolescence, and alopecia with a male pattern."
    },
    {
        "question": "What types of treatments were compared in the study regarding their effects on menstrual irregularities for women with polycystic ovarian syndrome?",
        "answer": "Auriculotherapy and medication."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the conclusion of the study regarding the long-term efficacy of auriculotherapy compared to medication?",
        "answer": "Auriculotherapy has a more long-term efficacy compared to medication, as its effects can be seen even up to 3 months after termination of the treatment."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is auriculotherapy and how does it differ from acupuncture?",
        "answer": "Auriculotherapy is the stimulation of auricles (external ears) to diagnose and treat diseases and preserve health, using methods like electric and seed stimulation instead of needles, and it is a branch of acupuncture."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the main objective of the seroprevalence study conducted in the Mbeya region of southwestern Tanzania?",
        "answer": "The main objective was to estimate TGR seroprevalence rates and to assess associated sociodemographic and environmental risk factors."
    },
    {
        "question": "How were the serum specimens for the substudy selected?",
        "answer": "The serum specimens were selected by stratified disproportionate random sampling from stored samples of participants in the second EMINI survey in 2007."
    },
    {
        "question": "On what basis were the serum samples tested for IgG against R. typhi considered positive?",
        "answer": "Serum samples with an IgG titer of 64 or higher were regarded as positive."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the significant predictors of TGR IgG included in the final multivariable model?",
        "answer": "The final multivariable model included age, vegetation density, and distance to the nearest highway as significant predictors of TGR IgG."
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the study hypothesize about using remote sensing data in relation to R. typhi infection?",
        "answer": "The study hypothesized that remote sensing data could be used to design a model for prediction of R. typhi infection, which could be used to direct public health interventions in the future."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the four principles of research ethics outlined in the article?",
        "answer": "Do no harm/non-maleficence, do good/beneficence, justice, and respect for autonomy."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why might public health researchers fail to apply for research ethics approval in low-income countries according to the article?",
        "answer": "The explanations include thinking that research ethics approval is not needed for researchers from high-income countries, not knowing the country has an ethics committee, applying to the wrong authority, worries about resource constraints, and assuming that there are exemptions for non-clinical public health research."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the two overarching themes that most explanations for the omission of seeking ethical approval fit into?",
        "answer": "Arrogance and ignorance."
    },
    {
        "question": "What should IRBs in high-income countries do when providing ethical approval for fieldwork in low-income countries?",
        "answer": "IRBs in high-income countries should only offer conditional ethical approval for fieldwork in low-income countries, with the main condition being that appropriate ethical approval should be sought locally too."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the article suggest is the final responsibility to ensure that public health research is conducted ethically?",
        "answer": "The final responsibility to ensure that public health research is conducted ethically lies with the researcher."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is orbital emphysema commonly caused by?",
        "answer": "Trauma and fracture of an orbital bone."
    },
    {
        "question": "What unusual symptom did the 67-year-old woman present with in the case study?",
        "answer": "Left exophthalmos."
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the computed tomography scanning reveal about the patient's condition?",
        "answer": "Left orbital emphysema and a remarkably enlarged left frontal sinus with a partial defect of the orbital roof."
    },
    {
        "question": "What surgical technique was used to treat the patient's orbital emphysema?",
        "answer": "Transcranial approach with drilling of the bone surrounding the sinus ostium and radical removal of mucosa in sinuses."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some potential causes of orbital emphysema besides trauma?",
        "answer": "Infection, complication of nasal surgery, sneezing, nose blowing, airplane travel, esophageal rupture, and frontal sinus pneumocele."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of cancer is oxaliplatin primarily used to treat?",
        "answer": "Advanced colorectal cancer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the main types of side effects associated with oxaliplatin?",
        "answer": "Neurotoxicity, mild hematological toxicity, and gastrointestinal symptoms"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is acute neurotoxicity characterized when it occurs as a side effect of oxaliplatin?",
        "answer": "By transient paresthesia and muscular spasm, often induced or aggravated by exposure to cold"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocular changes can oxaliplatin induce?",
        "answer": "Dry eyes, tearing, conjunctivitis, abnormal lacrimation, retinal damage, visual field cuts, blurred vision, visual loss, and altered color vision"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recommended response if a patient undergoing oxaliplatin therapy reports visual changes?",
        "answer": "A complete ophthalmologic examination must be performed, including complementary tests like computerized perimetry, OCT, and electrophysiological tests."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median survival rate for patients with distant metastases in breast cancer?",
        "answer": "The median survival rate is only two to three years."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is hormone receptor status critical in the treatment of metastatic breast cancer?",
        "answer": "Hormone receptor status is critical because treatment strategies are often tailored to the biology of the tumor, and information about hormone receptor status guides the preference for hormone therapies over systemic chemotherapy in most women with hormone-sensitive MBC."
    },
    {
        "question": "What has been the traditional treatment strategy for hormone-sensitive metastatic breast cancer, and how has it changed?",
        "answer": "The hormone treatment strategy was traditionally dominated by tamoxifen, but has been revised with the development of a novel class of hormone-targeting agents called aromatase inhibitors (AIs)."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main source of estrogen in premenopausal and postmenopausal women, respectively?",
        "answer": "In premenopausal women, the primary source of estrogen is the ovaries, while in postmenopausal women, estrogen is mainly produced from androgen precursors in adipose tissue."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the EFECT study and its significance in the treatment of hormone-sensitive metastatic breast cancer?",
        "answer": "The EFECT study was a clinical trial that compared intramuscular fulvestrant, a pure antiestrogen, with oral exemestane. It showed that some patients with tumor progression on a nonsteroidal AI can benefit from switching to a steroidal AI, with equivalent benefits to intramuscularly-administered hormone therapies."
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentage of new cancer cases and cancer deaths occur in patients older than 65 years?",
        "answer": "More than 60% of new cancer cases and 70% of all cancer deaths."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why are elderly cancer patients underrepresented in clinical trials?",
        "answer": "Underrepresentation may be due to explicit age restrictions, failure to meet eligibility criteria, concerns about comorbidities affecting treatment response, difficulty adhering to study procedures, concerns about toxicity, or the attitude of physicians, patients, and their families."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the primary goal of care for the 78-year-old patient with prostate cancer?",
        "answer": "To dance at his granddaughter's wedding in 3 months."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some domains of functional impairment that were associated with toxicity of chemotherapy according to the cancer and aging research group (CARG) study?",
        "answer": "Hearing impairment, falls, difficulty taking medications, limitations in walking one block, and decreased social activity."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the main reason the patient in the case study developed acute renal failure, and how was this addressed?",
        "answer": "The acute renal failure developed subsequent to methotrexate administration. It was addressed by dose reduction due to concerns about his renal function and the choice of a less toxic platinum agent."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the significance of the early work by Bergmann on Caribbean sponges?",
        "answer": "Bergmann's work on Caribbean sponges led to the isolation of the first arabino-nucleosides and inspired the development of clinically important antitumor drugs such as ara A and ara C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What compound is salvadenosine (1), and from which organism was it isolated?",
        "answer": "Salvadenosine (1) is an uncommon 5-deoxy-5-(methylthio) nucleoside, and it was isolated from an encrusting deep-water tunicate didemnum sp."
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the molecular formula of salvadenosine (1) established?",
        "answer": "The molecular formula of salvadenosine (1), C11H15N5O4S, was established from HRMS (ESI-TOF M/Z 312.0777 [M-H])."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the revised findings about hamiguanosinol's structure, and how was the revision confirmed?",
        "answer": "The revised findings indicated that the structure of hamiguanosinol is the keto tautomer 5, not the enol 2. This was confirmed by repeating the synthesis from guanosine and showing that the chemical shifts of the product matched those reported for natural hamiguanosinol."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is speculated as the biosynthetic origin of salvadenosine (1) from S-adenosylmethionine (SAM)?",
        "answer": "It is speculated that salvadenosine (1) may arise through displacement of 5-deoxy-5-(methylthio)adenosine from SAM, possibly through a LuxI-type mechanism with the release of homoseryl lactone, followed by the conversion to 1 by electrophilic or free-radical attack at C-8 with reactive oxygen species."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of Net Reclassification Improvement (NRI) in risk prediction models?",
        "answer": "The purpose of Net Reclassification Improvement (NRI) is to evaluate the improvement of risk prediction models by calculating the amount of correctly and incorrectly reclassified cases and non-cases when comparing classification into predefined risk categories between two nested models."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is there heterogeneity in the use and interpretation of NRI, as mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "There is heterogeneity in the use and interpretation of NRI because of the ongoing effort to improve prediction models, uncertainties related to testing statistical significance of NRI estimates, and the lack of established methods for inference for the NRI."
    },
    {
        "question": "How does the integration of family history as a new risk marker in the German Diabetes Risk Score (GDRS) impact the classification of diabetes risk?",
        "answer": "The integration of family history as a new risk marker in the GDRS impacts the classification of diabetes risk by causing reclassification of cases and non-cases across predefined risk categories, which can be measured by the NRI."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main limitation in the use of NRI that the article discusses?",
        "answer": "The main limitation in the use of NRI discussed in the article is the reliance on categories and cut-offs, which can be arbitrary and lack established thresholds for interpreting NRI values as meaningful for clinical or public health perspectives."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the advantage of using a confidence ellipse in the context of NRI, as opposed to evaluating single components separately?",
        "answer": "The advantage of using a confidence ellipse in the context of NRI is that it allows for the evaluation of the precision of the NRI estimates for cases and non-cases in combination and puts the results in the context of overall model improvement, reflecting the 2-dimensional nature of the situation."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is CKD-MBD and what are its components?",
        "answer": "CKD-MBD (Chronic Kidney Disease Mineral and Bone Disorder) is a syndrome currently defined by one or a combination of the following: abnormalities of calcium, phosphorus, parathyroid hormone, or vitamin D metabolism; abnormalities in bone turnover, mineralization, volume, linear growth, or strength; and/or vascular or other soft-tissue calcifications."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the gold standard for diagnosing renal osteodystrophy?",
        "answer": "The gold standard for diagnosing renal osteodystrophy is bone biopsy, as biochemical parameters do not adequately predict the underlying bone histology."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the term 'adynamic bone disease' (ABD) refer to, and what are its characteristics?",
        "answer": "Adynamic bone disease (ABD) refers to a type of disorder characterized by low bone turnover with normal mineralization, marked by an absence of osteoid accumulation, diminished number of osteoblasts, bone formation rate, and activation frequency."
    },
    {
        "question": "How does paricalcitol affect bone compared to calcitriol according to the in vitro study by Nakane et al.?",
        "answer": "According to the in vitro study by Nakane et al., paricalcitol caused less calcium release from mouse calvariae than did calcitriol, and it was the most effective preparation in stimulating collagen synthesis, contributing to its lower calcemic profile and possibly being more effective in stimulating bone formation."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the implication of a U-shaped curve in the context of parathyroid hormone (PTH) levels and mortality?",
        "answer": "The U-shaped curve implies that not only high but also low intact PTH plasma levels, as well as low PTH and high serum calcium levels (a combination typical for ABD), are associated with increased mortality, indicating a complex relationship between ABD, abnormal calcium balance, calcific arteriolopathy, vascular calcification, and mortality."
    },
    {
        "question": "What materials compose a DGT sampling unit?",
        "answer": "A DGT sampling unit consists of a resin gel, a diffusive gel, a protective membrane, and a sampler housing."
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the solute concentration at the sampler medium interface calculated according to the article?",
        "answer": "The solute concentration at the sampler medium interface is calculated using the 1D steady-state solution of Fick's first law of diffusion."
    },
    {
        "question": "What effects did Warnken et al. observe when they evaluated their experimental results using a physical sampling window surface area?",
        "answer": "Warnken et al. observed systematically higher cbdgt values compared to cb after correcting for the dbl-related mass uptake decrease."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the study, what was the effect of the diffusive boundary layer (dbl) on the solute uptake?",
        "answer": "The diffusive boundary layer (dbl) was found to significantly decrease the solute uptake."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the lateral diffusion flux increase coefficient (kld) and how is it defined?",
        "answer": "The lateral diffusion flux increase coefficient, kld, is defined as the ratio of the solute flux into the sampler in the 3D situation to the 1D flux, accounting for the effect of lateral diffusion at the sampler edges."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the pathology discussed in the article that involves ocular complications?",
        "answer": "Loiasis"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the main symptom that led to the baby being brought to the emergency room?",
        "answer": "Irritability, insomnia, painful red eye, photophobia, and tearing"
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the intraocular worm in the baby's eye eventually removed?",
        "answer": "Surgical intervention with a limbal-based incision and expulsion of the worm from the anterior chamber"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the lab analysis suggest about the identity of the worm after examining its physical characteristics?",
        "answer": "An adult male Loa loa worm"
    },
    {
        "question": "What treatment was given to the baby post-operatively?",
        "answer": "Bethamethason, a topical combination of dexamethason and neomycine, and atropine drops"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the importance of detecting colorectal cancer (CRC) at an early stage?",
        "answer": "Early detection of CRC can reduce mortality and improve survival rates."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why are scientists looking for new screening tools for colorectal cancer?",
        "answer": "Current screening methods like FOBT and colonoscopy have limitations and can result in false positives and negatives, and invasive methods can cause adverse effects."
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the methylation status of the sfrp2 gene used in the study?",
        "answer": "The methylation status of the sfrp2 gene in stool samples is used to screen and detect CRC in its early stages using methylation-specific polymerase chain reaction (MSP)."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the sensitivity and specificity percentages found for the sfrp2 gene marker in the study?",
        "answer": "For the sfrp2 gene, sensitivity was 60% and specificity was 92%."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the advantages of using DNA methylation as a biomarker for CRC screening?",
        "answer": "DNA methylation is a non-invasive method with high sensitivity, and can be used as an early diagnostic tool for CRC."
    },
    {
        "question": "What hypotheses did the study test regarding the paediatric intensive care population?",
        "answer": "The study tested the null hypotheses that the paediatric intensive care population weight distribution does not differ from that of the general population and that weight-for-age at admission does not influence risk-adjusted mortality."
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the weight of paediatric patients compared to the UK population reference data?",
        "answer": "The weight of paediatric patients was compared to the UK population reference data by calculating a weight-for-age standard deviation score (SDS), which is the number of standard deviations by which a weight value differs from the population mean."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the primary outcome of the study?",
        "answer": "The primary outcome was risk-adjusted mortality during paediatric intensive care unit (PICU) admission or within 30 days of discharge."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the study's findings, which weight-for-age group had the lowest risk of mortality?",
        "answer": "The lowest risk of mortality occurred in children with a weight-for-age at admission between 0.5 and 2.5 standard deviations above the UK mean weight-for-age."
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the study reveal about the relationship between weight-for-age at admission and risk-adjusted mortality?",
        "answer": "The study revealed a U-shaped association between weight-for-age at admission and risk-adjusted mortality, indicating the highest risk of mortality occurs with extreme under- or overweight."
    },
    {
        "question": "What neurological conditions are autism spectrum disorders (ASD) hypothesized to result from?",
        "answer": "ASD are hypothesized to result from synaptic dysfunction or synaptopathy."
    },
    {
        "question": "What association has been found in numerous studies regarding ASD?",
        "answer": "A strong association between imbalance in trace metal homeostasis and ASD has been reported in numerous studies."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the purpose of the experiments carried out on primary hippocampal neurons?",
        "answer": "The experiments were carried out to investigate the interplay and effects of a dyshomeostasis of different metal ions and the resultant pathological alterations of synapses."
    },
    {
        "question": "What effect did chronic treatment with metal chlorides have on synaptic parameters in the study?",
        "answer": "Chronic treatment of primary rat neuronal cultures with metal chlorides had an effect on various synaptic parameters, potentially causing synaptic defects."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was observed after zinc supplementation in the context of the ASD-like trace metal profile in cultured cells?",
        "answer": "After zinc supplementation, there was a significant reduction in dendritic fragmentation, a rescue in the number of synapses, and an increase in mRNA levels of certain synaptic receptors and proteins."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the purpose of optimizing the fat-1 cDNA coding region?",
        "answer": "The fat-1 cDNA coding region was optimized for mammalian cell expression."
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the mfat-1 expression cassette introduced into the C57BL/6 mice?",
        "answer": "The mfat-1 expression cassette was introduced into the C57BL/6 mice by pronuclear microinjection."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of enhancer and promoter were used in the mfat-1 expression cassette?",
        "answer": "The mfat-1 expression cassette used a cytomegalovirus (CMV) enhancer and a chicken beta-actin promoter tethered with a muscle creatine kinase (MCK) enhancer."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the study, what treatment did the adenovirus-infected INS-1 cells or islets receive after 48 hours of infection?",
        "answer": "The adenovirus-infected INS-1 cells or islets were exposed to cytokines which included interleukin-1 (IL-1), interferon-gamma (IFN-\u03b3), and tumor necrosis factor-alpha (TNF-\u03b1) for 48 hours."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the impact of mfat-1 expression on insulin secretion and cytokine-induced cell death?",
        "answer": "The expression of mfat-1 enhanced glucose, amino acid, and GLP-1 stimulated insulin secretion in isolated pancreatic islets and made the islets strongly resistant to cytokine-induced cell death."
    },
    {
        "question": "What symptom of bone cancer pain is considered highly debilitating to patients?",
        "answer": "Depression, anxiety, and functional status deterioration, all of which can severely affect the quality of life."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the purpose of understanding cellular and molecular mechanisms underlying bone cancer pain according to the article?",
        "answer": "Understanding these mechanisms is important for effectively treating patients with bone cancer pain."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which receptor's role was explored in the context of bone cancer pain in the study?",
        "answer": "The sigma-1 receptor."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the experimental treatment tested on rats to suppress mechanical allodynia and activation of spinal microglia in the study?",
        "answer": "Intrathecal administration of the selective sigma-1 receptor antagonist BD1047."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the outcome of using BD1047 in the treatment of bone cancer pain in the study?",
        "answer": "BD1047 significantly alleviated bone cancer-induced mechanical allodynia and suppressed the upregulation of certain molecules and expressions related to pain in the spinal cord."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did Korea achieve universal health insurance coverage?",
        "answer": "1989"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the initial groups covered by the national health insurance when it was first introduced in Korea in July 1977?",
        "answer": "All employees of large enterprises with 500 or more employees"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the main principles of the health insurance proposal recommended to the president of Korea in 1972?",
        "answer": "The program should follow market principles, expand population coverage gradually with economic recovery, invest in modernizing hospitals, and set medical fees through consultation with stakeholders"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the primary challenge faced by district health insurance societies in Korea?",
        "answer": "The lack of transparent income data and the resulting difficulty in setting up equitable contribution levels"
    },
    {
        "question": "What major step did Korea take in 2000 to improve its health insurance system?",
        "answer": "All insurer societies were merged into a single insurer called the Korean National Health Insurance Corporation (KHIC)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the genera of dermatophytes that cause infections in mammalian skin, nail, and hair?",
        "answer": "Trichophyton, Microsporum, and Epidermophyton"
    },
    {
        "question": "What recent advancements have helped in the precise identification and epidemiology of dermatophytes?",
        "answer": "Advancements in nucleotides sequencing and other DNA-based methods."
    },
    {
        "question": "During which time period was the study conducted that included dermatophyte strains from 500 culture-proven cases of dermatophytosis in Iran?",
        "answer": "From June 2011 to June 2012"
    },
    {
        "question": "What method was used to verify the presence of fungal elements in the study?",
        "answer": "Direct microscopic examination of skin scrapings, nails and hair shafts with 20% potassium hydroxide (KOH)."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which molecular technique was used for identification of dermatophytes in the study?",
        "answer": "PCR-RFLP on the beta-tubulin (BT2) gene."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main goal of a dentist when performing carious process excavation?",
        "answer": "The main goal of a dentist is to remove the irreversibly demineralised superficial tissue and the highly infected biomass of carious dentin."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why might new restorative materials have difficulty adhering to heavily infected dentin tissue?",
        "answer": "New restorative materials have difficulty adhering to heavily infected dentin tissue if it is retained at the cavity floor because of the infection."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the clinical markers that dentists use to guide the excavation of infected, demineralised dentin?",
        "answer": "Dentists commonly use hardness/texture of the tissue, its color, and may use caries detector dyes as clinical markers to guide the excavation of infected, demineralised dentin."
    },
    {
        "question": "How do caries detection dyes work, and what should not be done when using them?",
        "answer": "Caries detection dyes consist of 1% acid red in propylene glycol and stain the demineralised dentin light pink. Light pink stained dentin should not be removed to prevent excessive dentin removal."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the aim of the study comparing ECM, LF, and CDD in detection of residual dentinal caries in excavated cavities?",
        "answer": "The aim of the study was to compare histologically the efficiency of ECM, LF, and CDD in detection of residual dentinal caries in excavated cavities and assess their accuracy, sensitivity, specificity, and inter- and intraobserver accuracy."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the role of autophagy in maintaining cellular homeostasis?",
        "answer": "Autophagy plays an important role in developing and maintaining cellular homeostasis by targeting aged or malfunctioning organelles and damaged or misfolded proteins for lysosomal degradation."
    },
    {
        "question": "How has the inhibition of autophagy been shown to affect cancer cells?",
        "answer": "The pharmacological and/or genetic inhibition of autophagy can sensitize cancer cells to the lethal effects of various cancer therapies, such as chemotherapy, radiotherapy, and targeted therapies."
    },
    {
        "question": "What triggers the induction of autophagy as detailed in the article?",
        "answer": "Nutrient starvation results in mTOR inhibition and induction of autophagy."
    },
    {
        "question": "What method was suggested as an alternative to GFP-labeling and electron microscopy for monitoring autophagy regulation in tissues?",
        "answer": "Immunohistochemistry (IHC) was suggested as an alternative method for assessing autophagy regulation in tissues in clinically relevant settings."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function of ATG7 in the process of autophagy, and what happens when it is knocked down?",
        "answer": "ATG7 is an E1 activating enzyme that is essential for lipid conjugation of autophagy-specific ubiquitin-like proteins, necessary for autophagosome formation. Knockdown of ATG7 reduces UBL lipidation and slows down the basal constitutive autophagy process, leading to the accumulation of autophagy adapter proteins like p62 and NBR1."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the common term for a peritonsillar abscess?",
        "answer": "Quinsy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which bacteria are considered key causative pathogens in PTA?",
        "answer": "Streptococcus pyogenes, Fusobacterium necrophorum and Streptococcus milleri group"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the main treatment methods for PTA mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "Needle aspiration, surgical drainage, quinsy tonsillectomy combined with antimicrobial therapy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of study was conducted to explore the PTA epidemiology, clinical history and microbiology in Radom, Poland?",
        "answer": "A retrospective study"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the percentage of PTA patients with a history of recurrent pharyngotonsillitis in the Polish study?",
        "answer": "35.5%"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is hepatic encephalopathy due to intrahepatic portosystemic venous shunts without portal hypertension?",
        "answer": "It is a rare condition where there is a vascular anomaly defined as a communication between the portal and systemic venous circulations inside the liver."
    },
    {
        "question": "When is interventional treatment for IPSVS considered necessary?",
        "answer": "Interventional treatment for IPSVS is required if the conservative treatments for hepatic encephalopathy, such as restriction of protein and administration of nonabsorbable antibiotics and lactulose, are not sufficiently effective."
    },
    {
        "question": "What treatment did the patient with hepatic encephalopathy due to congenital multiple IPSVS undergo?",
        "answer": "The patient was successfully treated by percutaneous transhepatic obliteration, which included transcatheter embolization of the causative vessel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What changes were observed in the patient's condition following the transcatheter embolization for IPSVS?",
        "answer": "The serum ammonia level normalized the day after the endovascular shunt closure, and neither hyperammonemia nor consciousness disorders occurred during the 5-year follow-up period after embolization."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is patient follow-up after embolization necessary according to the article?",
        "answer": "Patient follow-up with upper gastrointestinal endoscopy and contrast-enhanced CT scan after embolization is necessary for detecting portal hypertension-related complications such as ascites and bleeding of esophagogastric varices."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the initial laboratory tests results that indicated the 48-year-old woman had a non-ST elevation myocardial infarction?",
        "answer": "Elevated serum cardiac enzymes, specifically creatine kinase-MB at 14.8 ng/ml and troponin I at 3.44 ng/ml."
    },
    {
        "question": "Despite having no traditional risk factors for coronary artery disease, what condition was eventually diagnosed in the 48-year-old woman?",
        "answer": "Antiphospholipid syndrome (APS), which was postoperatively diagnosed due to intraoperative findings of diffuse coronary artery thrombosis and positive lupus anticoagulant activity."
    },
    {
        "question": "What surgical procedure did the 48-year-old woman undergo due to her intractable chest pain and coronary artery lesions?",
        "answer": "Off-pump coronary artery bypass (OPCAB) using a skeletonized right internal thoracic artery (ITA) graft."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the outcome of the 1-year postoperative angiogram for the 48-year-old woman?",
        "answer": "The angiogram demonstrated completely resolved left anterior descending (LAD) lesions, a patent graft to the ramus intermedius and diagonal coronary arteries, and a competitive flow pattern in the graft to the LAD coronary artery."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Antiphospholipid syndrome (APS) and how is it diagnosed?",
        "answer": "APS is a clinical syndrome associated with antibodies against phospholipids, manifesting as systemic thrombotic disorders. It is diagnosed based on at least one clinical feature\u2014vascular thrombosis and/or pregnancy morbidity\u2014and one of the laboratory criteria, which are lupus anticoagulant and/or anticardiolipin antibody."
    },
    {
        "question": "What has modern management of heart failure in children come to consider beyond just normalizing cardiac output and improving symptoms?",
        "answer": "Modern management of heart failure in children also considers neuroendocrine stimulation, myocyte remodeling, cellular energetics, and connective tissue/myocyte interactions."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary mechanism of action of beta-blocking agents in chronic heart failure, according to the acceptable hypothesis?",
        "answer": "The primary mechanism of action of beta-blocking agents in chronic heart failure is to prevent and reverse adrenergically-mediated intrinsic myocardial dysfunction and remodeling."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the specific aim of the study conducted on patients with beta-thalassemia major?",
        "answer": "The study aimed to evaluate the safety and efficacy of carvedilol in patients with beta-thalassemia major who have a common cause of cardiomyopathy and heart failure."
    },
    {
        "question": "How were the patients enrolled in the carvedilol study for beta-thalassemia major grouped and treated?",
        "answer": "Patients were randomly assigned to two groups, with group 1 receiving carvedilol and group 2 receiving a placebo. Carvedilol was started at a dosage of 3.12 mg bid and could be increased every two weeks to a maximum of 25 mg bid if tolerated."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was a significant finding at the end of the 6-month follow-up regarding the ejection fraction in the study of carvedilol on patients with beta-thalassemia major?",
        "answer": "At the end of the 6-month follow-up, patients in the carvedilol group had the same ejection fraction as the control group."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are bromodomains and why are they significant in the context of this article?",
        "answer": "Bromodomains are acetyl-lysine specific epigenetic reader domains and are significant because they are an emerging target class for the design of protein interaction inhibitors that selectively modulate gene transcription."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why has the discovery of potent and selective inhibitors mainly focused on the BET subfamily of bromodomains?",
        "answer": "The discovery of potent and selective inhibitors has mainly focused on the BET subfamily of bromodomains because the first inhibitors for this subfamily have reached clinical testing, whereas no potent and selective inhibitors are known for the large majority of other bromodomains."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the role of the protein complex BAZ2A-NORC, and why are mutations in the BAZ2A bromodomain significant?",
        "answer": "The BAZ2A-NORC protein complex, a member of the imitation switch chromatin remodeling complexes (ISWI), regulates the expression of noncoding RNAs and establishes a repressive heterochromatic structure at centromeres and telomeres. Mutations in the BAZ2A bromodomain that abolish histone binding impair the association of NORC with chromatin and transcriptional repression, which is significant for proper gene regulation."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unexpected finding in the cocrystal structure of compound 1 bound to BAZ2B?",
        "answer": "The unexpected finding in the cocrystal structure of compound 1 bound to BAZ2B was that the hydrophobic phenyl ring of 1 occupied the acetylated lysine (Kac) binding pocket, despite the presence of conserved water molecules and the asparagine residue, which typically act as hydrogen bond donors."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the significance of compound 13 (BAZ2-ICR) in the context of this research?",
        "answer": "Compound 13 (BAZ2-ICR) is significant because it represents a potent and selective chemical probe of the BAZ2 bromodomains, which satisfies the criteria for a dual BAZ2A and BAZ2B chemical probe with an excellent in vitro and in vivo profile, aiding in the investigation of the biological role of BAZ2A and B."
    },
    {
        "question": "What advantage do high-throughput methods provide in gene expression analysis?",
        "answer": "High-throughput methods allow for the generation of detailed temporal expression data for a single gene or large numbers of genes."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a challenge in comparing temporal expression data?",
        "answer": "A challenge is comparing data obtained from different growth conditions where the patterns of expression may be shifted in time."
    },
    {
        "question": "What analytical method does the article propose for comparing temporal expression patterns?",
        "answer": "The article proposes the use of wavelet analysis to compare temporal expression patterns from experiments with time shifts or delays."
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the wavelet analysis approach demonstrated in the article?",
        "answer": "The wavelet analysis approach was demonstrated using detailed temporal data for a single bacterial gene obtained under 72 different growth conditions."
    },
    {
        "question": "Can the general strategy described be applied to larger datasets, and if so, how extensive can these datasets be?",
        "answer": "Yes, the general strategy can be applied to the analysis of data sets of thousands of genes under different conditions."
    },
    {
        "question": "What genetic pattern does incontinentia pigmenti (IP) follow for inheritance?",
        "answer": "Incontinentia pigmenti is inherited by an X-linked dominant gene."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the major diagnostic criteria for incontinentia pigmenti?",
        "answer": "The major criteria for diagnosing incontinentia pigmenti include a typical neonatal vesicular rash with eosinophilia, typical blaschkoid hyperpigmentation on the trunk that fades in adolescence, and linear, atrophic hairless lesions."
    },
    {
        "question": "At what age did the skin lesions start appearing in the 5-year-old male child described in the article?",
        "answer": "The skin lesions started appearing at 1 week of age in the form of vesicular lesions on the lower extremities, which gradually spread onto the trunk."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is the role of dermatologists and pediatricians crucial in the context of incontinentia pigmenti?",
        "answer": "The role of dermatologists and pediatricians is crucial in early diagnosis of incontinentia pigmenti."
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there a specific test for incontinentia pigmenti and how is it diagnosed?",
        "answer": "There is no specific test for incontinentia pigmenti; diagnosis is typically based on clinical features and can be supported with genetic testing and DNA analysis."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between secondary leukemia and de novo leukemia?",
        "answer": "Secondary leukemia refers to the appearance of a new, biologically unrelated leukemia following the treatment of the primary malignancy, while de novo leukemia refers to leukemia in patients without prior exposure to potentially leukemogenic therapies or agents."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is more common to lead to secondary acute myeloid leukemia (AML), treatment for hematologic disorders or solid tumors?",
        "answer": "Treatment for hematologic disorders is more common to lead to secondary acute myeloid leukemia (AML)."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is secondary AML rare following allogeneic HSCT for AML?",
        "answer": "Secondary AML is rare following allogeneic HSCT for AML primarily because the anti-leukemic effects of the allogeneic graft reduce the risk of a secondary clone developing."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the new complex cytogenetic abnormalities identified in the patient's second AML?",
        "answer": "The new complex cytogenetic abnormalities included abnormal chromosomes such as der(y)t(y;15), del(1)(q32), t(1;3)(p36.1;q21), inv(3)(p21q25), add(4)(p16), del(7)(q22), +8, inv(9)(p13p24), -15, add(16)(p13.3), and del(13)(q12q22)."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the significant features of the patient's case presented in the article?",
        "answer": "The patient exhibited a longer latency period than in previous reports of secondary AML following hematologic and/or non-hematologic malignancies, rare cases of secondary AML following de novo AML, and the second AML might be biologically unrelated to the first due to its new complex cytogenetic aberrations."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is healthy aging defined as according to the article?",
        "answer": "Healthy aging is defined as aging without disease."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some of the determinants of neuronal vulnerability mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "Determinants of neuronal vulnerability include altered protein interaction networks, mitochondria, reactive oxidative species and intracellular calcium homeostasis, autophagy, signal transduction pathways, stem cell proliferation, and stress resistance mechanisms."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which brain regions are most susceptible to age-related changes in prefrontal cortex and white matter?",
        "answer": "The prefrontal cortex and white matter are most susceptible to age-related changes."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the variability in cognitive ability and its decline associated with brain aging suggest according to recent studies?",
        "answer": "Studies suggest that age-related cognitive decline is more likely to be associated with alterations in synaptic connectivity than with neuronal loss and white matter changes."
    },
    {
        "question": "How does the concept of 'cognitive reserve' relate to aging and neuroplasticity?",
        "answer": "The concept of 'cognitive reserve' relates to the ability to reinforce brain volume in certain areas and provide a greater threshold for age-dependent deficits, as well as the capacity of the brain to manage pathology or age-related changes, thereby minimizing clinical manifestation."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the initial symptoms experienced by the 9-year-old boy from La Gamba, R\u00edo Claro?",
        "answer": "The initial symptoms were fever, cough, and malaise."
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the rabies virus likely transmit to the boy and the woman?",
        "answer": "The likely transmission was through a cat bite, where the cat could have been previously infected by a bat."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal's variant of the rabies virus was found in both patients?",
        "answer": "A rabies virus variant associated with vampire bats was found in both patients."
    },
    {
        "question": "What measures were taken after the diagnosis of rabies in the patients?",
        "answer": "Rabies postexposure prophylaxis with a vero cell rabies vaccine was administered to the relatives of the patients and to veterinary and healthcare personnel."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the GIS operation do to help in the fight against rabies?",
        "answer": "The GIS operation defines areas of low, medium, and high-risk of disease, helping to identify risk zones for optimal control and prevention of rabies."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most prevalent cause of chronic liver diseases mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "Nonalcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) is the most prevalent cause."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the estimated percentage of adults affected by NAFLD in Iran?",
        "answer": "It is estimated that 35% of adults in Iran are affected by NAFLD."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, what types of nutrients have some studies suggested people with NAFLD intake less of?",
        "answer": "Some studies suggest that patients with NAFLD have a lower level intake of vitamin D and antioxidant vitamins (E and C), as well as calcium and zinc."
    },
    {
        "question": "What dietary factor did the study find to be higher in individuals with NAFLD compared to healthy individuals?",
        "answer": "The study found that the intake of saturated fat and sugar is higher in individuals with NAFLD compared to healthy individuals."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the criteria for inclusion in the control group of the study?",
        "answer": "Inclusion criteria for the control group were volunteers who were the neighbors of the case group and were the same as them in age and sex, with wellbeing in the case of NAFLD approved (not suffering from any stages of hepatic steatosis)."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the purpose of adding 1 g/L or 4.5 g/L of glucose to the CS-CF medium in the experiment?",
        "answer": "The purpose was to create normal glucose and high glucose conditions for incubating human umbilical vein endothelial cells (HUVECs) for screening study purposes."
    },
    {
        "question": "What method was used to determine esRAGE production in the cell culture-derived supernatants?",
        "answer": "Colorimetric ELISA under the manufacturer's protocol was used to determine esRAGE production."
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the peroxynitrite scavenging activity expressed in this study?",
        "answer": "The peroxynitrite scavenging activity was expressed as percentage inhibition of the control A500 nm."
    },
    {
        "question": "What result indicated that certain plant samples had potent inhibitors of 8-OHdG?",
        "answer": "The calculated 8-OHdG recovery rates for the plant samples, which were significantly lower than the control, indicated that the samples were potent inhibitors of 8-OHdG."
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the results suggest about the correlation between esRAGE production and total phenolic content (TPC) of the methanolic extracts?",
        "answer": "The results suggested a positive correlation between esRAGE production and TPC, indicating that the phenolic content of the plants could be attributed to their esRAGE production."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why has the use of the axillary artery as a percutaneous access site lost favor?",
        "answer": "The use of the axillary artery as a percutaneous access site has lost favor due to the success of procedures from radial or brachial alternatives and concerns such as its proximity to the neurovascular bundle, uncertainty of its ability to accommodate larger sheaths, and difficulties in effecting hemostasis."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some of the alternative access points mentioned for percutaneous intervention, and what is their limitation?",
        "answer": "Some of the alternative access points for percutaneous intervention are the radial and brachial arteries, and their limitation is typically being unable to accommodate anything larger than a 6 or 7 fr sheath."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the hypothesis regarding the axillary artery size in relation to the common femoral artery?",
        "answer": "The hypothesis was that the axillary artery would not only be of comparable size to the common femoral artery in most patients but also be less frequently calcified or diseased and able to accommodate sheaths with up to an 18 fr outer diameter in the vast majority of patients."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the results of the study comparing the sizes of the axillary artery and common femoral artery?",
        "answer": "The study found that the mean sizes of the right and left axillary arteries were 6.38 mm and 6.52 mm, respectively, versus 8.26 mm and 8.2 mm for the right and left common femoral arteries, with a mean difference of 1.69 mm between the axillary artery and common femoral artery."
    },
    {
        "question": "What percentages of axillary and common femoral arteries demonstrated calcification in the study, and what does this imply about the suitability of axillary artery as an access site?",
        "answer": "Only 1.04-2.1% of axillary arteries demonstrated calcification, versus 17.8-19.8% of common femoral arteries, indicating a significantly lower percentage of calcification in the axillary arteries, implying it may be a suitable access site for certain procedures."
    },
    {
        "question": "What layers are responsible for producing catecholamine and mineralocorticoids in the adrenal glands?",
        "answer": "The medullar layer is responsible for producing catecholamine while the cortical layer produces mineralocorticoids."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the most common types of tumors found in the adrenal glands?",
        "answer": "The most common tumors found in the adrenal glands are cortical adenomas without hormonal hyperfunction."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which imaging techniques are recommended for assessing the suprarenal areas?",
        "answer": "Ultrasound is the method of choice, particularly in neonates and children, while computed tomography and magnetic resonance imaging are preferred for assessing adrenal pathologies in adolescents and adults."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some causes of Addison's disease in developed countries?",
        "answer": "Addison's disease can be caused by tuberculosis, metastases to both adrenal glands and destruction by a neoplastic process such as lymphoma."
    },
    {
        "question": "What should be included in the description of an ultrasound examination of adrenal glands in neonates?",
        "answer": "The description should include the size of the gland and the presence of possible focal lesions."
    },
    {
        "question": "How many receptor-binding members are there in the FGF family, and what do they regulate?",
        "answer": "There are 18 receptor-binding members in the FGF family, and they regulate a broad spectrum of cellular activities."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function of the FRS2 and FRS2 proteins in FGF signaling?",
        "answer": "FRS2 and FRS2 are membrane-anchored adaptor proteins that are required for the FGF to activate the MAP and PI3 kinase pathways, which are the two major pathways in the FGF signaling cascade."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the consequences of FRS2 null mutations in mouse embryos?",
        "answer": "FRS2 null mouse embryos die between embryonic days 7.0 and 7.5."
    },
    {
        "question": "What role does FRS2 play in the regulation of autophagy according to the study?",
        "answer": "FRS2 is required for the FGF signaling axis to activate the mTOR pathway and to suppress the autophagy activity in MEFs."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which domains are shared between FRS2 and FRS2, and what are their functions?",
        "answer": "FRS2 and FRS2 share similar structure domains, which include the N-terminal myristylation site that anchors FRS2 to the cell membrane, the phosphotyrosine-binding (PTB) domain required for binding to the FGFR, and the C-terminal sequence that contains multiple tyrosine and serine/threonine phosphorylation sites."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main age group affected by tuberculosis according to the study?",
        "answer": "The main age group affected by tuberculosis is 15 - 55 years."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some of the reasons that tuberculosis rates are higher among poor populations?",
        "answer": "Deprivation associated with poverty increases the risks of tuberculosis infection and development of disease, and factors like inadequate ventilation and lighting, overcrowded housing, and indoor air pollution due to biomass fuel in cooking."
    },
    {
        "question": "What methods were used to collect data for the tuberculosis study in Dhubri district?",
        "answer": "Data was collected using a pre-tested structured questionnaire through interviews with the patients at their residences."
    },
    {
        "question": "What factors influenced the patients' compliance with tuberculosis treatment in the study?",
        "answer": "Factors influencing compliance included distance to the treatment center, unpleasant drug effects, personal inconvenience like needing to work for livelihood, insufficient knowledge, individual cost during treatment, and for women, interaction with health staff and social stigma."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the study results, how did early treatment affect the cure rate for tuberculosis?",
        "answer": "91.84% were declared cured among patients who came for treatment within the first 6 weeks after the onset of symptoms, whereas only 40% of those who came for treatment from 6 weeks to 6 months after the onset of symptoms were declared cured."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of the intraoperative squash smear technique?",
        "answer": "The primary purpose of the intraoperative squash smear technique is for the rapid and simple diagnosis of brain tumors during surgery."
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the squash smear technique used in the study?",
        "answer": "In the study, the squash smear technique involved crushing tissue obtained during operation between two glass slides, fixing the smears in alcohol, staining them, and then having them reported by a consultant pathologist."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the compatibility rate between cytological and histopathological diagnoses in the study?",
        "answer": "The compatibility rate between cytological and histopathological diagnoses in the study was 94.0%."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some of the challenges mentioned in the article regarding intraoperative cytological diagnosis?",
        "answer": "Some of the challenges regarding intraoperative cytological diagnosis include misrepresentation of tumor tissue, difficulty smearing certain types of tumors, and variations within a single tumor that can affect grading."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why might a pathologist request additional tissue to be submitted intraoperatively?",
        "answer": "A pathologist might request additional tissue to be submitted intraoperatively if the tissue is not representative or the cytology findings are not consistent with radiology, as this could help reduce diagnostic discrepancies."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a cavernous malformation and what are its other names?",
        "answer": "A cavernous malformation (CM), also known as cavernous angioma or cavernoma, is a vascular malformation characterized by the presence of sinusoid-like capillary vessels containing blood with poor circulation."
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Lawton et al. define a giant cavernous malformation (GCM)?",
        "answer": "Lawton et al. defined a giant cavernous malformation (GCM) as a CM with a diameter greater than 6 cm."
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the key findings from the MRI and CT scans of the patient in the case study?",
        "answer": "The MRI and CT scans revealed a well-defined cystic mass with a size of 7.2*4.6 cm filled with a 2 cm intra-cystic nodule on the left fronto-parietal lobe, showing low signal intensity in T1-weighted images and high signal intensity in T2-weighted images."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the initial diagnosis based on imaging findings before the histological examination confirmed the mass was a CM?",
        "answer": "The initial diagnosis based on imaging findings was a low-grade glioma, congenital infection such as toxoplasmosis or cytomegalovirus, or even neurocysticercosis."
    },
    {
        "question": "What surgical approach was taken to treat the patient's cavernous malformation in the case study, and what was the outcome?",
        "answer": "A left frontal craniotomy followed by a transcortical approach was taken to treat the patient's cavernous malformation, with cyst aspiration and intra-cystic nodule removal, resulting in an improvement in the patient's right-sided motor weakness with no complications."
    },
    {
        "question": "How are coarse and fine controls in metabolic regulation different according to the textbook perspective?",
        "answer": "Coarse control refers to long-term mechanisms that are energetically expensive and lead to changes in the total cellular population of a protein, while fine control describes fast, energetically inexpensive regulatory devices that modulate the activity of pre-existing enzyme molecules."
    },
    {
        "question": "What recent advancement in technology has allowed a massive amount of data regarding steady-state RNA levels?",
        "answer": "The recent advancement in technology that has allowed a massive amount of data regarding steady-state RNA levels is afforded by microarrays and next generation sequence analyses."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the three mechanisms mentioned in the article that include metabolic regulation in plants?",
        "answer": "The three mechanisms include alteration in substrate or co-substrate concentration, variation in pH, and allosteric effectors."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the role of quantitative trait loci (QTL) analysis in plant genetic studies?",
        "answer": "QTL analysis helps in understanding the genetic basis of quantitative traits by identifying particular genomic regions showing statistically significant associations with trait variation, despite their complex multigenic inheritance and strong interactions with the environment."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why are the studies on rice particularly pertinent from an applied perspective?",
        "answer": "The studies on rice are particularly pertinent from an applied perspective because rice is the staple food crop of almost half of the world's population, and understanding its genetic and metabolic diversity can be highly valuable for breeding programs."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the reported biomedical applications under development for nanoscale materials?",
        "answer": "Drug delivery systems targeted to the brain and cancer tissues, gene transfection, and intravascular nanosensor and nanorobotic devices for imaging and diagnosis."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of properties do fullerenol C60(OH)24 exhibit?",
        "answer": "Fullerenol C60(OH)24 exhibits properties such as being potent free-radical scavengers and antioxidants, acting as glutamate receptor antagonists, antiproliferative, neuroprotective, and anticancer agents."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why may many biomedical studies involving fullerenol species in the literature need to be reconsidered?",
        "answer": "Because it has been found that most fullerenols are not pure C60(OH)n, but rather a complex mixture of different products, thus affecting the accuracy of the studies."
    },
    {
        "question": "What method was used to prepare the pure fullerenol C60(OH)24 used in the study?",
        "answer": "The pure fullerenol C60(OH)24 was prepared by a modified method of alkaline hydrolysis of C60Br24, followed by demetallation with a cation exchange resin and exhaustive purification by dialysis."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main binding mode of fullerenol C60(OH)24 to DNA according to the study?",
        "answer": "Hydrogen bonding to the phosphate backbone to the outside of the dsDNA helix is the main binding mode of fullerenol C60(OH)24 to DNA."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Huntington's disease (HD) characterized by?",
        "answer": "Huntington's disease is characterized by a triad of progressive motor dysfunction, cognitive decline, and psychiatric disturbances."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the genetic mutation causing Huntington's disease localized and what does it result in?",
        "answer": "The genetic mutation causing Huntington's disease is localized to the short arm of chromosome 4, resulting in an expansion and instability of a cytosine-adenine-guanine (CAG) repeat in gene IT15, producing unstable huntingtin protein."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the typical age of onset and duration for Huntington's disease?",
        "answer": "The typical age of onset for Huntington's disease is in the fourth to fifth decade of life, and the condition gradually worsens over 10 to 20 years until death."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some of the psychiatric symptoms and their prevalence in Huntington's disease patients?",
        "answer": "Psychiatric symptoms in Huntington's disease patients include both neurotic and psychotic disorders, with a prevalence significantly higher than in the general population, estimated to be around 66-73%. Psychotic symptoms occur in about 3-11% of patients, while a more specific schizophrenia-like psychosis occurs in 3-6% of patients."
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the unique aspect of the patient's case presented in the article?",
        "answer": "The unique aspect of the patient's case was the subsequent onset of Huntington's disease in a patient who was previously treated for schizophrenia and who experienced extrapyramidal side effects to antipsychotics."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main diagnostic criterion related to Levodopa (LD) responsiveness in Parkinson's Disease (PD)?",
        "answer": "The main diagnostic criterion related to Levodopa responsiveness in PD is required to exceed a 25%-30% reduction in the motor part of the Unified Parkinson's Disease Rating Scale (UPDRS)."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why do physicians sometimes delay using Levodopa in the treatment of Parkinson's Disease?",
        "answer": "Physicians sometimes delay using Levodopa due to concerns about the potential induction of long-term motor complications such as drug-induced dyskinesia."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the motor complications associated with long-term treatment with LD?",
        "answer": "The motor complications associated with long-term treatment with LD include the development of various types of motor response oscillations over the day and drug-induced dyskinesia, characterized by erratic involuntary movements."
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the CALM-PD trial compare, and what was the primary outcome measure?",
        "answer": "The CALM-PD trial compared initial treatment with the agonist pramipexole versus Levodopa-carbidopa, with the primary outcome measure being the time to first occurrence of dopaminergic complications like wearing-off, dyskinesias, 'on-off' fluctuations, and freezing."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the proposed reason why Levodopa (LD) may induce motor complications?",
        "answer": "The proposed reason why Levodopa may induce motor complications is the discontinuous and intermittent delivery of LD to the brain, resulting in nonphysiologic pulsatile stimulation of striatal dopamine receptors due to the short half-life of immediate-release LD formulations."
    },
    {
        "question": "What condition was the 45-year-old female patient being treated for?",
        "answer": "The patient was being treated for Complex Regional Pain Syndrome (CRPS)."
    },
    {
        "question": "What symptoms did the patient suffer from in her left upper extremity?",
        "answer": "The patient suffered from allodynia and hyperalgesia in her left upper extremity."
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of block was performed on the patient to manage her symptoms?",
        "answer": "A left unilateral thoracic paravertebral block at the second thoracic vertebral level was performed."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did the patient return to the clinic three hours after the procedure?",
        "answer": "The patient returned to the clinic complaining of left chest pain and mild dyspnea."
    },
    {
        "question": "What ultrasound findings led to the diagnosis of pneumothorax in the patient?",
        "answer": "The absence of the lung sliding sign and comet-tail artifact at the pleural line led to the diagnosis of pneumothorax."
    }
]